undercovercondoms.com 2016-11-03

# Undercover Condoms - Privacy Policy

## We Take Your Privacy Very Seriously

When shopping with Undercover Condoms you can rely on the following: 

  * All transactions occur through our secure server, protected by SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) Certificate.
  * We use the latest security procedures and data collection methods to ensure your personal information is safe and secure.
  * Personal information and payment information is encrypted and stored securely in our database.
  * We will never sell your email, phone number, or any other personal information to any individual or entity outside of our company.

## Privacy Statement

Undercover Condoms, owned and operated by PCPD, LLC. collects information about its customers both during the order process and as customers navigate the undercovercondoms.com web site. The information provided by customers during the ordering process such as their name, physical address, email address, and payment information is considered private, and Undercover Condoms will not sell this personal information to third parties. This information will be used to process your order and deliver it to you in a timely fashion. In addition, Undercover Condoms reserves the right to contact existing customers regarding store specials and other significant events if they have choosen to opt in to our email marketing service. 

## Opt-Out Provided

Undercover Condoms will provide existing customers with the opportunity to "opt-out" or choose to be removed from future mailings from Undercover Condoms. Opt-out information will be included with any non-personal or non-essential message sent to prior customers. You may also Opt-Out by sending an email to [service@undercovercondoms.com](mailto:service@undercovercondoms.com) requesting that you be removed from certain types of future mailings or calling 800-893-9105. A personal or essential message is one that would relate directly to the particular customer's order. 

## Non-Personal Information

Undercover Condoms also routinely collects statistics on site usage patterns through web logs, web beacons and third party service providers. These statistics are not intended to relate to any particular individual. Instead, they are used internally to judge the effectiveness of web site features and content. Some real-time information is occasionally used to automatically suggest a product to a customer based on that customer's observed preferences. 

We use cookies on this site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use session ID cookies to allow visitors to easily navigate during checkout and access their account information. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We use a persistent cookie to welcome visitors returning to the site and to associate appropriate advertisements for our visitors. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site. Without a session ID cookie, your ability to complete a purchase and checkout will be limited. 

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, and tracking utility company is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, and tracking utility company use session ID cookies to make it easier and safer for you to navigate our site. 

Our third party partners employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers' or Users' personally identifiable information. 

We partner with a third party ad network to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by [clicking here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

## Third Party Service Providers

Undercover Condoms may share your information provided with your order with third-party service providers who provide services related to your order. Examples of these third-party service providers include a credit card processing company, a supplier, or a shipping service. Your personal information will not be used by any third party for purposes other than providing these services in relation to your order. 

## Links to 3rd Party Sites

Our site may include links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Undercover Condoms. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. 

## Social Media Widgets

Our website includes social media features in conjuction with Facebook, Twitter, Pintrest and Google+. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

## Blogs

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [service@undercovercondoms.com](mailto:service@undercovercondoms.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

## Testimonials

We sometimes display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [service@undercovercondoms.com](mailto:service@undercovercondoms.com). 

## Legal Disclosure of Your Information

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. If Undercover Condoms is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

## Contests and Drawings

Undercover Condoms may sponsor or host contests or drawings from time to time. Some contests may be offered in conjunction with a third party sponsor and website users will be notified at the time of the contest as to whether a third party sponsor is involved and whether the third party will be receiving the user's information to send promotional communications. The website user can then choose whether to enter the contest or not at that time based on the terms and conditions associated with that particular contest. 

## Transaction Security

All transactions occur through our Secure Server, protected by a SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) certificate. That means that we use encryption to secure information sent from your computer to our servers. In addition, credit card numbers and other sensitive information is encrypted in our database to provide a second layer of security for your private information. 

## Updating Your Information

If you ever need to update or delete any information on file with Undercover Condoms, you may call or email us at [service@undercovercondoms.com](mailto:service@undercovercondoms.com). If you need to update your information when re-ordering, you will have a chance to make changes to your payment information, shipping and billing addresses at checkout. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We may also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

If you have additional questions about the privacy of your information, please contact Undercover Condoms at [service@undercovercondoms.com](mailto:service@undercovercondoms.com) or call us at 800-893-9105. 

## Mailing Address

##### Undercover Condoms

##### Columbus, Ohio 43228

##### 2199 Dividend Dr

##### United States

Last Updated On: 7/1/2015 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage prior to the change becoming effective.
